{
    "subject": "Marty_Feldman",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "In_God_We_Tru$t",
    "human_readable": "Marty Feldman created In God We Tru$t.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9061489701271057,
            "question": "Did Marty Feldman write the screenplay for In God We Tru$t?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8278722763061523,
            "question": "Who created the film In God We Tru$t?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6017277836799622,
            "question": "What is the significance of the title 'In God We Tru$t'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5982165336608887,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in In God We Tru$t?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5817320942878723,
            "question": "What year was In God We Tru$t released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5621020197868347,
            "question": "What is the name of the film created by Marty Feldman?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4740707576274872,
            "question": "How was In God We Tru$t received by critics and audiences?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4476563334465027,
            "question": "What genre is In God We Tru$t likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4291171133518219,
            "question": "Was Marty Feldman known for a particular acting style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20413166284561157,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by Marty Feldman?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marty Feldman created In God We Tru$t.",
            "html": "yago_27936_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Marty Feldman known for a particular acting style?",
            "html": "yago_27936_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is In God We Tru$t likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_27936_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How was In God We Tru$t received by critics and audiences?",
            "html": "yago_27936_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27936_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Marty Feldman created In God We Tru$t\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while Marty Feldman directed, co-wrote and starred in the film \"In God We Tru$t\", there is no mention of him creating it. The documents suggest that he produced, directed, and co-wrote the film, but do not use the word \"created\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information that supports the statement that Marty Feldman created (\"directed and co-wrote\") the film \"In God We Tru$t\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information shows that Marty Feldman wrote and directed In God We Tru$t, but also clearly states \"It's a satire of religious figures, televangelists and the state of religion in modern times. / It's a satire of religious figures...\" which means that he did not create it, satires are created by one person writing (in this case) 2 others wrote with him (Chris Allen).",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}